

# Tarek BEN YAHIA

# **Future Software Engineer**

Currently student in 5th and last year of my studies in software engineering cycle, I'm searching for an end-of-studies internship .I chose mobile development as a specialty and I really enjoy it . I have a good experience working with Flutter and Native Android ,acquired thanks to my academic projects and freelance experience .I also have some graphic design and web development skills that I developed during my first years at the university. I am a very curious person, I always want to learn new things and new technologies and work with them to develop my skills. I like working in a team, it allows me to learn new things among other things. I am also very dynamic, and good communicator.

# +216 24 760 280

Tarek.benyahia@esprit.tn

Tunis,Tunisia

Click to Visit Website

in Click to visit my LinkedIn

Click to Visit my Github

### **SKILLS**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Critical thinking

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

Flutter | Android | Node.JS | HTML | CSS | PHP | JAVA | Kotlin | SQL | JavaScript | MongoDB | Github | Docker | Symfony | Angular

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Arabic Maternal
- French Bilingual
- English B2
- German B2

#### Clubs and associative life

- 2017-2019 : AIESEC Member (Marketeer)
- 2018-2020 :Inceptum Junior Entreprise Member at sales pole

# **EDUCATION**

- ESPRIT( Private High School of Engineering and Technologies) | 2016 Today
  - ✓ Software Engineering Degree
- Pioneer School of Ariana | 2012 2016
  - √ Tunisian Baccalaureate (Experimental Sciences)

# **EXPERIENCE**

- Freelancer | 2017 To Today
  - Mobile development (Android , Flutter, Node. JS (Backend))
  - Web development (Symfony)
  - Graphic Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, After effects, Premiere Pro)
- Arduino Trainer | 2017 To Dec 2018
  - Association Jeunes Science de Tunisie (AJST), Tunisia
  - Teached kids from 7 to 18 basics of Arduino programming
- Web Developer | 2018 To Dec 2020
  - Print Group, Tunisia
  - Web Development using Symfony
- Mobile Development Internship(Flutter) | 2019 2020
  - Scar Interactives, Tunisia
  - > Frontend application with Flutter
  - Backend Development using Node.JS
- Mobile Development Internship(Android) | July 2021 To Sept 2021
  - Yes-SERV Architecture, Tunisia
  - > Frontend application with Android
  - Backend Development using Node.JS

# **ACADEMIC PROJECTS** (Group projects)

- 2D Video Game | 2016-2017
  - Developed using SDL (C Language)
- \* CRM Platform | Sept. 2017 To Jan. 2018
  - Developed with QT (C++)
- E-Commerce Website | Jan. 2018 To June 2018
  - Developed with Native php
- Hunting management platform | Sept.2019 May 2020
  - > 3 Platforms: Web (Symfony), Desktop (JavaFX), Mobile (Android) + SCRUM Methodology
- Barter Mobile Application | Sept. 2020 To Dec. 2020
  - Developed with Native Android and Node.JS
- Cross-Platform Application for Lawyers | Jan. 2020 To June 2020
  - Developed with Flutter (mobile) ,Angular (Web) and Node.JS + Docker + SCRUM Methodology

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Introduction to HTML5(University of Michigan)(Coursera)
- Introduction Psychology (YALE University)(Coursera)
- Fundamentals of Graphic Design (California Institute of the Arts)(Coursera)
- Java For Android (Vanderbilt University)(Coursera)
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (Google Digital Garage)
- Multiplatform Mobile App Development with React Native (The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology)(Coursera)
- The French language test (TCF)